var question = {

    q1: {
        question: "1.witch kind of sport,there is no ball ?",
        1: "football",
        2: "swim",
        3: "basketball",
        4: "soccer",
        correct: "2"
    },

    q2: {
        question: "2.When was the recognition of the State of Israel ?",
        1: "1948",
        2: "2000",
        3: "1950",
        4: "1967",
        correct: "1"
    },

    q3: {
        question: "3.Who was Israel's first prime minister ?",
        1: "David Ben Gorion",
        2: "Bibi",
        3: "Rabin",
        4: "Begin",
        correct: "1"
    },

    q4: {
        question: "4.What is the capital of Israel ?",
        1: "New York",
        2: "Netanya",
        3: "Jerusalem",
        4: "Tel Aviv",
        correct: "3"
    },

    q5: {
        question: "5.What is the capital of Spain ?",
        1: "Barcelona",
        2: "Madrid",
        3: "Tel Aviv",
        4: "New York",
        correct: "2"
    },

    q6: {
        question: "6.What is the capital of France ?",
        1: "Pariz",
        2: "Madrid",
        3: "Tel Aviv",
        4: "New York",
        correct: "1"
    },

    q7: {
        question: "7.What animal is under water ?",
        1: "Lion",
        2: "Fish",
        3: "Cat",
        4: "Dog",
        correct: "2"
    },

    q8: {
        question: "8.Who is the best friend of man ?",
        1: "Lion",
        2: "Fish",
        3: "Cat",
        4: "Dog",
        correct: "4"
    },

    q9: {
        question: "9.What is unusual ?",
        1: "Lion",
        2: "Fish",
        3: "Cat",
        4: "Dog",
        correct: "2"
    },

    q10: {
        question: "10.What is the capital of Egypt ?",
        1: "Cairo",
        2: "Madrid",
        3: "Tel Aviv",
        4: "New York",
        correct: "1"
    }

}
